Guide to the Artistic Autographs Collection, 1800-1869
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Artistic Autographs Collection
1800-1869
2.1 cubic feet (7 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
A set of correpondence to and from various artists, art collectors and art dealers. Correspondents include Elias Magoon and John Britton.
Scope and Content Note
A set of correpondence to and from various artists, art collectors and art dealers. Correspondents include Elias Magoon and John Britton.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Subject Headings
Names:
Magoon, Elias Lyman; Britton, John, 1771-1857
Subjects:
Artists--Autographs; Artists--19th century
Document Types:
autographs (manuscripts)
VCL Categories
Art and Artists
Encoding Information
Finding aid encoded by Jason Kovari, 12 Feb 2009.
Acquisition Information
This collection may have been acquired by the Vassar College in conjunction with the Magoon art collection, now housed at the Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center.
Container List
- Eginton, H. to "My Dear Sir,", 7 July 1835 (1.1)
- Britton, John to Eginton, H., 28 Jan [1835?] (1.2)
- Eaton, Thomas to Britton, John, 9 Feb 1822 (1.3)
- Eaton, Thomas to [Britton, John], 2 Mar 1822 (1.4)
- Eaton, Thomas to [Britton, John], 10 Mar 1823 (1.5)
- Millers, G. [Rev.] to Britton, John, 13 July 1806 (1.6)
- Soane, George to Britton, John, undated (1.7)
- Soane, Geo[rge] to Britton, John, undated (1.8)
- Bedford, Dr. to "Sir,", 5 June 1804 (1.9)
- "To Mr. Britton,", 29 May n.y. (1.10)
- Children, J[ohn] G[eorge] to "My dear Sir,", 21 Apr 1834 (1.11)
- Nichols, John Bowyer to "My dear Sir,", 21 Apr 1834 (1.12)
- Britton, John to Donaldson, H., 6 Mar 1837 (1.13)
- [letter], 2 Oct 1838 (1.14)
- Willson, Edward James, undated (1.15)
- Windows, undated (1.16)
- Baptisteries, undated (1.17)
- [Bridges], undated (1.18)
- [Jerusalem, The Church of the Holy Sepulcher, Reference to Plan], undated (1.19)
- [Towers], undated (1.20)
- [France to Germany], undated (1.21)
- Soane, John to Britton, John and Mr. Wrightwich, Dec 1839 (1.22)
- Snow, W. "Reminiscence of the Soane portrait,", undated (1.23)
- [London Bridge], undated (1.24)
- Soane, John, undated (1.25)
- [?], 9 Jan [18?] (1.26)
- [Letter], undated (1.27)
- Walford, Thomas to "Dear Sir,", 18 Nov 1818 (1.28)
- Extract from the Vestry Book, Cirencester, 1671 (1.29)
- Anecdotes of the late Sir John Soane, undated (1.30)
- Nisard. Histoire et description... Nimes, 1835 (1.31)
- Notice historique sure Notre to Dame de Paris, 1836 (1.32)
- Soane, John. A statement of the facts…, undated (1.33)
- Grose, Francis [transcripts of his letters to various people], undated (1.34)
- Doors, undated (1.35)
- Soane, John, undated (1.36)
- [letter], undated (1.37)
- [From Tour in Germany by John Russell...], 1824 (1.38)
- Britton, John. "Saints & Sinners" to Soane, John, undated (1.39)
- Bridges, undated (1.40)
- Porches, undated (1.41)
- Britton, John. "On Porches" to paper for Architect’s Institute, 12 June 1843 (1.42)
- [document to Portico], undated (1.43)
- ["order of toasts"], undated (1.44)
- Soane’s Museum; Soane to Britton, Dec. 2, 1825; Desc. Of Church at E. Dereham, 2 Dec 1825 (1.45)
- Fry, William Thomas to "Sir,", undated (2.1)
- Burton, Decimus to "My dear Sir,", 4 June 1829 (2.2)
- Knight, William [Henry?] to Britton, John, undated (2.3)
- Blenham, Matthew Holbecke to Britton, John, 17 Feb 1843 (2.4)
- Cobett, William to "My dear Sir,", undated (2.5)
- Repton, John Adey to Ellis, Henry, [1827] (2.6)
- Goldicutt, John to Britton, John, 22 Apr 1834 (2.7)
- Wightwick, George to "Dear Sir,", 25 May 1827 (2.8)
- Soane, John to "Dear Sir,", 15 Oct 1809 (2.9)
- Soane, John to Britton, John, undated (2.10)
- Soane, George to Britton, John, 5 Aug 1838 (2.11)
- Smith, Sally to Britton, John, 19 Jan 1847 (2.12)
- Re: Soane, undated (2.13)
- Welch, R. to "My dear Sir,", 20 Apr 1847 (2.14)
- Turner, Charles to Soane, John, 16 Feb 1833 (2.15)
- Soane, John to "My dear Sir,", 31 July 1834 (2.16)
- Soane, John to "Dear Sir,", undated (2.17)
- Soane, John to "My Dear Sir,", undated (2.18)
- Soane, John to [Brown?], 10 Jan 1832 (2.19)
- Soane, John to Britton, John, 16 Feb 1829 (2.20)
- Soane, John to "My Dear Friends,", 12 Sept 1826 (2.21)
- Soane, John to [Britton, John], 28 Dec 1822 (2.22)
- Willson, James to Britton, John, 18 Dec 1812 (2.23)
- Soane, John to Britton, John, July 1829 (2.24)
- Soane, John to "Dear Sir,", 6 Apr [1804?] (2.25)
- Soane, John to [Britton, John], 9 Apr 1817 (2.26)
- Soane, George to Britton, John, [1837] (2.27)
- Taylor, James to "Dear Sir,", 20 Sept 1831 (2.28)
- Soane, John to [Britton, John], Apr 1827 (2.29)
- Soane, John to [Comm?], P.C., 1 Dec [1800?] (2.30)
- Soane, John to Britton, John, undated (2.31)
- Knight, William [Henry?] to [Britton, John], Oct 1827 (2.32)
- [letter], undated (2.33)
- Burton, James to Britton, John, 21 June [1825?] (2.34)
- Material between letters 46 & 47, undated (2.35)
- Stuart, Dudley Coults to Wagstaff, C. E., 2 Jan 1850 (3.1)
- Croly, George to Wagstaff, C. E., 16 Mar 1843 (3.2)
- Dale, Thomas to "My Dear Sir,", 7 May 1847 (3.3)
- Grey, Earl to Stuart, Lord Dudley, 31 Dec 1869 (3.4)
- Raddon, William to "Dear Sir,", 31 Oct 1836 (3.5)
- Harding, James Duffield to Wagstaff, C. E., 27 June 1850 (3.6)
- Frith, William Powell to Wagstaff, C. E., 3 Dec 1842 (3.7)
- De la Motte, Phillip Henry to Le Keux, J.H., 4 Dec 1849 (3.8)
- Ward, Thomas to Wagstaff, 22 June 1849 (3.9)
- Lance, George to "My Dear Friend,", undated (3.10)
- Clint, George to Wagstaff, Cornelius, 22 Jan 1837 (3.11)
- Allen, James Baylis to Wagstaff, Mr., 28 June 1850 (3.12)
- Haydon, Benjamin R. to Wagstaff, C. E., 26 July 1843 (3.13)
- Carew, John E. to The Committee at Manchester, 20 Jan 1837 (3.14)
- Humphreys, William to Wagstaff, Charles E., 16 Feb 1842 (3.15)
- Russell, Lord William to Wagstaff, Mr., 16 Apr 1839 (3.16)
- Biard to Monsieur, 29 May 1827 (3.17)
- Duncan, Edward to Wagstaff, C. E., 27 June 1850 (3.18)
- Hussey, Richard Charles to Le Keux, J.H., 11 Nov 1856 (3.19)
- Bone, C.R. to "Sir,", 27 June 1850 (3.20)
- Donaldson, to Wagstaff, Mrs., 25 Feb 1857 (3.21)
- Clint, Alfred to Wagstaff, undated (3.22)
- Bacon, Frederick to Wagstaff, C. E., undated (3.23)
- Brandard, John to Wagstaff, C. E., 26 June 1850 (3.24)
- Pye, John to Wagstaff, C. E., undated (3.25)
- Hayter, George to Graves, N, 6 Nov 1844 (3.26)
- Burford, Robert to Wagstaffe, G.G., 1 July 1850 (3.27)
- Watt, James Henry to "Dear Sir,", undated (3.28)
- Inskipp, James to Wagstaff, 9 Jan 1835 (3.29)
- Parris, Edmond Thomas to "Dear Sir,", [24 Dec 1849?] (3.30)
- Duncan, Thomas to Wagstaff, Mr., 17 Mar 1843 (3.31)
- Lupton, Thomas to Wagstaff, C. E., 28 Sept 1842 (3.32)
- Phillips, Thomas to Wagstaff, E., 21 June 1837 (3.33)
- Fairland, Thomas to Wagstaff, C. E., 27 Feb 1843 (3.34)
- Pickersgill, Henry Hall to Wagstaff, C. E., 13 Oct 1843 (3.35)
- Brockedon, William to [?], 22 Mar 1843 (3.36)
- Bartholomew, Valentine to Wagstaff, C. E., 28 June 1850 (3.37)
- Neiman [N.?] to Wagstaff, C. E., 1849 (3.38)
- Leslie, Charles Robert to Wagstaff, C. E., 20 Mar n.y. (3.39)
- Green, Benjamin Richard to Wagstaff, C. E., 3 Nov 1848 (3.40)
- Phillips, Thomas to Wagstaff, C. E., 27 May 1841 (3.41)
- Mulready, William, Jr. to "Dear Sir,", 16 June n.y. (3.42)
- Collins, William to "Dear Sir,", undated (3.43)
- Lawrence, Thomas to [?], 24 July 1828 (3.44)
- Ritchie, L to Wagstaffe, Mrs., 6 May n.y. (3.45)
- Woodman, Richard to Wagstaff, C. E., 30 Dec 1845 (3.46)
- Roberts, David to Wagstaff, C. E., undated (3.47)
- Stanfield, Clarkson to "Gentlemen,", 23 Jan 1844 (3.48)
- Heath, Charles to John Britton [?], 9 July 1844 (3.49)
- Wild, James William to [?], undated (3.50)
- Smirke, Sydney to Le Keux, J.H., 28 Apr 1848 (3.51)
- D’Orsay, Count to "Dear Sir,", 25 Nov 1848 (3.52)
- Sharpe, Edmund to Le Keux, J.H., 22 May 1848 (3.53)
- Le Keux, Henry to "Dear John,", 29 Feb 1839 (3.54)
- Le Keux, Henry to "My Dear John,", 27 Apr 1857 (3.55)
- Parker, John Henry to Le Keux, J.H., 10 Apr 1848 (3.56)
- Billings, Robert William to Le Keux, J.H., 11 Sept 1848 (3.57)
- Bliss, Dr. Philip to Le Keux, J.H., 20 Nov 1854 (3.58)
- Jones, Henry Longueville to Le Keux, J.H., 7 Jan 1858 (3.59)
- Chesney, Francis Rawdon to Le Keux, J, 6 June 1843 (3.60)
- Smirke, Robert to "Sir,", 25 Aug 1828 (3.61)
- Corbould, Henry to Le Keux, Mr., 1 June n.y. (3.62)
- Wright, Thomas to Le Keux, J.H., 19 May n.y. (4.1)
- Le Keux, John Sr. to "My Dear Sir,", 31 Aug 1844 (4.2)
- [?] to Britton, John, undated (4.3)
- [?], undated (4.4)
- Roberts, David to Britton, John, 14 May 1846 (4.5)
- Foggo, George to Britton, John, 21 Mar 1838 (4.6)
- Masquerier, J[ohn] J[ames] to Britton, John, 12 Dec 1836 (4.7)
- Ward, F. O. to "Dear Sir,", 16 Oct 1845 (4.8)
- Nash, John to Britton, John, 20 Feb 1819 (4.9)
- Ross, W[illiam] C[harles] to "Dear Sir,", 8 Oct 1846 (4.10)
- Allom, T[homas] to "My Dear Sir,", 20 Mar 1842 (4.11)
- Wightwick, George to Britton, John, 6 Apr 1846 (4.12)
- Pickersgill, H[enry] W[illiam], 13 July 1831 (4.13)
- Hosking, Wm. to Britton, John, 16 June 1835 (4.14)
- Parris, Edmond Thomas to John Britton, 30 Dec n.y. (4.15)
- Harding, J[ames] D[uffield], undated (4.16)
- Higham, Thomas to "Sir,", undated (4.17)
- Heath, C[harles] to Britton, John [?], [30 May 1834 ?] (4.18)
- Radclyffe, W[illiam] to "Dear Sir,", 23 [Dec 18?] (4.19)
- Noble, Samuel to Britton, John, 14 Nov 1828 (4.20)
- Sands, R. to "Dear Sir,", undated (4.21)
- Britton, John to [Ansted, Henry?], 5 July 1823 (4.22)
- Robinson, G.W. to Britton, John, 27 June 1827 (4.23)
- Rickman, J[ohn] to Britton, John, 1 [or 12?] Feb 1836 (4.24)
- Pye, John to Britton, John, 28 May 1829 (4.25)
- Finden, W[illiam] to Britton, John, 15 Oct 1834 (4.26)
- Bury, [Lady] Charlotte [Susan] Maria to Mr. Moyes [James?], 28 June 1833 (4.27)
- De La Warr, Earl to Britton, John, 7 June 1836 (4.28)
- Northampton, Marquis of to "Dear Sir,", 26 Aug 1841 (4.29)
- Courtenay, Earl to [Crary, Esq.], 6 July 1801 (4.30)
- McLellan, Archibald to Britton, John, 16 Apr 1835 (4.31)
- Hall, [J.I.?] to Britton, John, 12 Sept 1854 (4.32)
- Johnson, D.L. [Miss] to "My dear Sir,", 21 Nov 1829 (4.33)
- Adamson, John to Britton, John, 13 Nov. 1841 (4.34)
- Brockedon, William to Moyes, James, 13 June 1828 (4.35)
- Bliss, Dr. Philip to Mr. Moyes [James?], 1 Nov 1827 (4.36)
- Galt, John to Mr. Moyes [James], 22 July 1834 (4.37)
- Johnston, Alexander, Jr. to Moyes, James, 22 Dec 1829 (4.38)
- Leach, J. (Col.) to Moyes, James, 30 Oct 1831 (4.39)
- Leigh, S. to Moyes, James, 20 Nov 1847 (4.40)
- Lamb, Henry to Moyes, James, 10 Mar 1815 (4.41)
- Raffles, [Rev. Dr.] Thomas to Moyes, James, 30 June 1830 (4.42)
- Lee, Samuel [Rev. Dr.] to Moyes, James, 17 Jan 1837 (4.43)
- Lee, Sara to "Dear Sir,", 14 Nov 1837 (4.44)
- Soane, John to Moyes, W., 15 Sept 1832 (4.45)
- Ainsworth, William Harrison to Britton, John, 23 Mar 1842 (4.46)
- Yates, James to Britton, John, 26 Oct 1839 (4.47)
- Martineau, Joseph to Britton, John, 11 June n.y. (4.48)
- Moffatt, W.B. to Britton, John, 16 Sept 1846 (4.49)
- Cunningham, Peter to Britton, John, 29 June 1847 (4.50)
- Brooke, Arthur to Britton, John, 6 June 1830 (4.51)
- Boswortth, James to Gould, N., 19 Nov 1847 (4.52)
- Moffatt, John to "Dear Sir,", 11 Nov 1826 (4.53)
- Maunder, Samuel to "Dear Sir,", 3 Oct 1829 (4.54)
- Mackintosh, R.D. to Britton, John, 7 Feb 1835 (4.55)
- Malkin, Benjamin Heath to "My dear Sir,", 5 Feb 1826 (4.56)
- Mudford, William to Britton, John, 7 Mar 1821 (4.57)
- Mudford, William to Britton, John, 23 Mar n.y. (5.1)
- Murdoch, Menardes to Britton, John, 10 Oct 1846 (5.2)
- Moseley, W.M. to Britton, John, 23 Jan 1813 (5.3)
- Monteith, William to Britton, John, 1 Apr n.y. (5.4)
- Noble, J. to Britton, John, 9 Mar1814 (5.5)
- Nicholson, Alexander to "My dear Sir,", 2 July 1842 (5.6)
- Nichols, John Bowyer to Britton, John, 20 May 1844 (5.7)
- Burges, A. to Britton, John, 5 May 1846 (5.8)
- Rhodes, Ebenezer to "Dear Sir,", 25 Apr 1822 (5.9)
- Moon, Francis Graham to Britton, John, 6 Jan 1834 (5.10)
- Munder, Thomas to Britton, John, 19 Jan 1838 (5.11)
- Miller, Thomas to Britton, John, 17 Dec 1838 (5.12)
- Carter, J. to "Honoured Sir,", 30 Dec. 1845 (5.13)
- Croker, Thomas Crofton, "My dear Sir,", 27 July 1838 (5.14)
- Blewitt, Octavian to Britton, John, 4 Mar 1840 (5.15)
- Neeld, Joseph to "dear Sir,", 10 Feb 1834 (5.16)
- Kemp, John to Britton, John, 14 Mar 1840 (5.17)
- Holmes, John to "My dear Sir,", 27 Nov 1834 (5.18)
- Kendall, Edward Augustus to Britton, John, 6 Apr 1839 (5.19)
- Christie, James to Britton, John, 9 May 1822 (5.20)
- Bray, Anna Elizabeth to "My dear Sir,", 11 June 1849 (5.21)
- Brown, Thomas to Britton, John, 6 May 1840 (5.22)
- Alexander, G. to Britton, John, 1 July 1846 (5.23)
- Meyrick, Samuel Rush to "Dear Sir,", 28 Aug 1812 (5.24)
- Akerman, John Yonge to "My dear Sir,", 10 May 1847 (5.25)
- Hobhouse, Benjamin to Britton, John, 13 May 1819 (5.26)
- Mavor, William Fordyce to Britton, John, 9 June 1808 (5.27)
- Mantell, Gideon [Algernon] to Britton, John, 18 Jan 1834 (5.28)
- Sharp, Daniel to Cox, Rev. F. A., 25 Apr 1844 (5.29)
- Choate, Rufus to "Dear Sir,", 5 Dec 1842 (5.30)
- Story, Joseph to Griggs, George, 23 Apr 1840 (5.31)
- White, George H. to Magoon, Elias L., 28 Apr 1860 (5.32)
- Webster, Fletcher to Everett, Edward, 31 May 1860 (5.33)
- Périn, [Alphonse?] to Magoon, Elias L., 22 Aug 1859 (5.34)
- Avery, Samuel Putnam to "My Dear Sir" [Elias Magoon?], undated (5.35)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 27 Apr n.y. (5.36)
- Beaumont, Georgine de to Magoon, Elias L., 10 Dec 1859 (5.37)
- Everett, Edward to Magoon, Elias L., 31 May 1860 (5.38)
- Collins, R. to Magoon, Elias L., 11 Dec 1859 (5.39)
- Everett, Edward to Magoon, Elias L., 30 May 1860 (5.40)
- Petit, John Louis to Magoon, Elias L., 27 Feb 1856 (5.41)
- Britton, John to Magoon, Elias L., 9 Nov 1855 (5.42)
- Everett, Edward to Magoon, Elias L., 22 Nov 1856 (5.43)
- Everett, Edward to Magoon, Elias L., 23 Nov 1858 (5.44)
- Lockwood, Rembrandt to Magoon, Elias L., 4 Dec 1856 (5.46)
- Wyld, William to Magoon, Elias L., 14 Aug 1857 (5.47)
- Gifford, Sanford Robinson, 9 Apr 1860 (5.48)
- Périn, [Alphonse?] to "Cher Monsieur,", 10 Nov 1859 (5.49)
- Wyld to William to Magoon, Elias L., 11 Sept 1858 (5.50)
- Weir, Robert Walter to Magoon, Elias L., 17 Mar 1856 (5.51)
- White, Edwin to Magoon, Elias L., [1856] (5.53)
- Chappel, Alonzo to Magoon, Elias L., 19 Nov 1858 (5.54)
- Mount, William Sidney to Magoon, Elias L., 6 Apr 1856 (5.55)
- Shattuck, Aaron Draper to Magoon, Elias L., 7 Mar 1860 (5.56)
- Wickes, P to Le Keux, J, 20 Aug n.y. (6.1)
- Le Keux, J. H. to Magoon, Elias J., 9 Nov 1855 (6.2)
- Smyth, William Henry –"My Dear Sir,", 6 June 1842 (6.3)
- Viney, James to "Dear Sir,", 19 Nov 1826 (6.4)
- Merridew, John to Britton, John, 3 Feb 1831 (6.5)
- Markland, James Heywood to "My Dear Sir,", 26 Dec 1846 (6.6)
- Mears, Thomas to "Dear Sir,", undated (6.7)
- Currer, Frances Mary Richardson to "Sir,", 7 Dec 1808 (6.8)
- Jackson, Thomas to Britton, John, 5 May 1867 (6.9)
- Layton, William to Britton, John, 10 Feb 1829 (6.10)
- Cresy, Edward to Britton, John, 16 July 1839 (6.11)
- Coll, Henry to "Dear Sir,", 4 Nov 1843 (6.12)
- Fell [Fels?], Edward to "My dear Sir,", undated (6.13)
- Grellier, William to Britton, John, 24 Nov 1840 (6.14)
- Shield, William to "Dear Sir,", 13 May 1823 (6.15)
- Landon, W to Britton, J[ohn], 7 Nov 1838 (6.16)
- Gasper, D to "My Dear Sir,", 24 Nov 1836 (6.17)
- Anonymous [Trundens?] to Britton, J, 16 Feb 1818 (6.18)
- Goldicutt, John to Britton, J[ohn], 6 Feb 1839 (6.19)
- Blakeway, John Brickdale to Britton, John, 8 Aug 1814 (6.20)
- Burney, Charles Parr to "Dear Sir,", 18 May 1806 (6.21)
- Cartwright, Edmund to "Dear Sir,", 24 Apr 1830 (6.22)
- Cliffe, C.F. to Britton, J[ohn], 14 Sept 1847 (6.23)
- Godwin, William to Britton, J[ohn], 28 Nov 1828 (6.24)
- King, Edward [?] to Britton, J[ohn], 13 Feb 1801 (6.25)
- Malcolm, J. P. to "Dear Sir,", undated (6.26)
- Morice, J to "Dear Sir,", 26 June 1841 (6.27)
- Nares, Robert to Britton, John, 11 Mar 1811 (6.28)
- Miller, W to Britton, J[ohn], 3 Jan 1841 (6.29)
- Man [or Marr?], John to Brayley and Britton, 8 Oct 1804 (6.30)
- Hoare, P to "Dear Sir,", 31 Jan 1802 (6.31)
- Hughes, John to Britton, J[ohn], 26 Mar 1821 (6.32)
- Taylor, John to Britton, John, 10 Sept 1812 (6.33)
- Ormerod, George to Britton, J[ohn], [7 May 1835?] (6.34)
- Upham, Edward to "My Dear Sir,", 1 May (6.35)
- Omerod, George to Britton, J[ohn], 20 Apr 1807 (6.36)
- Vincent, William to "Sir,", undated (6.37)
- Vivian, George to Britton, J[ohn], 3 June 1847 (6.38)
- Wyse, Thomas to Britton, J[ohn], 17 Jan 1846 (6.39)
- Yarrell, William to Britton, John, 8 Sept 1854 (6.40)
- Palarowe [?] Francis to Britton, J[ohn], undated (6.41)
- Edmonds, Richard Jr. to [?], 11 Apr 1857 (6.42)
- Wellbeloved, Charles to Britton, J[ohn], 16 Feb 1843 (6.43)
- Delamotte, P.H. [?] to Le Keux, J. H., undated (6.44)
- Virtue, George to "My Dear Sir,", 20 Nov 1846 (6.45)
- Bidder, George Parker to Britton, J[ohn], 8 August 1839 (6.46)
- Walker, Ellen Loveday to Britton, John, 10 Mar 1828 (6.47)
- Peel, Robert to Britton, J[ohn], 2 Dec n.y. (6.48)
- Vigors, Nicholas Aylward to Britton, John, 1 July 1829 (6.49)
- Lockhart, John Gibson to "My Dear Sir,", 25 July 1843 (6.50)
- Willson, Edward James to Britton, J[ohn], 22 Feb 1813 (6.51)
- Mullen, J to "My Dear Sir,", 22 May 1846 (6.52)
- Nichols, John Gough to Britton, J[ohn], 9 July 1833 (6.53)
- Prouis, John to Britton, John, 5 Nov 1824 (6.54)
- Boone, W to "Dear Sir,", undated (6.55)
- Parden, C.F. to "Dear Sir,", 8 Sept 1817 (6.56)
- Crawford, Louisa M.J.M. to Britton, J[ohn], 10 Aug 1843 (6.57)
- Watts, Susanna to "Sir,", 8 May 1807 (6.58)
- Haggard, William Henry to Britton, J[ohn], 17 May 1820 (6.59)
- La Vosperne to Britton, J[ohn], 6 Dec 1819 (6.60)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 9 May 1858 (7.1)
- Everett, Edward to Magoon, Elias L., 30 May 1860 (7.2)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 5 May 1858 (7.3)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 3 Sept 1856 (7.4)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 4 Sept 1856 (7.5)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 10 Nov 1856 (7.6)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 7 Jan 1859 (7.7)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 26 Feb 1857 (7.8)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 8 May 1857 (7.9)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 2 July 1857 (7.10)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 10 Sept 1857 (7.11)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 5 Jan 1858 (7.12)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 6 Apr 1858 (7.13)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 31 Dec 1858 (7.14)
- Le Keux, J[ohn] H[enry] to Magoon, Elias L., 12 Jan 1860 (7.15)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 25 Jan 1860 (7.16)
- Le Keux, John Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 16 Mar 1860 (7.17)
- Le Keux, John henry to Magoon, Elias L., 12 Oct 1859 (7.18)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 15 July 1855 (7.19)
- Ruskin, J[ohn] to Magoon, Elias L., 17 Jan n.y. (7.20)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 8 Oct n.y. (7.21)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 14 May n.y. (7.22)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 5 Feb n.y. (7.23)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 21 Apr 1857 (7.24)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 25 Sept 1858 (7.25)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 15 Dec 1856 (7.26)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 9 Oct n.y. (7.27)
- Ruskin, John to Magoon, Elias L., 15 Nov 1856 (7.28)
- White, George H. to Magoon, Elias L., 18 July 1856 (7.29)
- White, George H. to Magoon, Elias L., 3 Sept 1858 (7.30)
- White, George H. to Magoon, Elias L., 26 Feb 1858 (7.31)
- White, George H to Magoon, Elias L., 12 Aug 1859 (7.32)
- White, George H. to Magoon, Elias L., 9 Sept 1859 (7.33)
- Page, Julius to Magoon, Elias L., 23 Jan 1857 (7.34)
- Buckley, J.E. to Magoon, Elias L., 17 May 1855 (7.35)
- Swain, James B to Magoon, Elias L., 22 June n.y. (7.36)
- Greene, Edward D.E. to Magoon, Elias L., 27 July 1861 (7.37)
- Champney, Benjamin to Magoon, Elias L., 14 Sept 1861 (7.38)
- Moore, Charles Herbert to Magoon, Elias L., 26 May 1861 (7.39)
- Beaumont, Georgine de to Magoon, Elias L., 26 May 1861 (7.40)
- Périn, Alphonse to Magoon, Elias L., [6 July 1859?] (7.41)
- Richards, William Trost to Warren, George B., Jr., 4 Apr 1861 (7.42)
- Shattuck, Aaron Draper to Magoon, Elias L., 17 May 1861 (7.43)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin to Magoon, Elias L., 29 Apr 1858 (7.44)
- Webster, Daniel to "My Dear Sir,", 14 Oct 1828 (7.45)
- Everett, Edward to Magoon, Elias L., 17 Oct 1860 (7.46)
- Schaus, W. to Magoon, Elias L., 5 Sept 1860 (7.47)
- Weale, John to Magoon, Elias L., undated (7.48)
- Farrer, Thomas Charles to Magoon, Elias L., undated (7.49)
- Rogers, John to Magoon, Elias L., 7 Nov n.y. (7.50)
- Griggs, S.W. to "Dear Sir,", undated (7.51)
- [Poem?], undated (7.52)
- Avery, Samuel Putnam to "Dear Friend,", undated (7.53)
- Gerry, Samuel L. to Magoon, Elias L., 22 Sept 1860 (7.54)
- Beard, William Holbrook to Magoon, Elias L., 17 Oct 1859 (7.55)
- Nichols, Edward W. to Magoon, Elias L., [22 Oct 1861?] (7.56)
- Hart, William to Magoon, Elias L., 27 Nov n.y. (7.57)
- Church, Frederic Edwin to Palmer, [Erastus Dow?], 27 Dec 1858 (7.58)
- Young, J. H. to Magoon, Elias L., 22 Jan n.y. (7.59)
- Sanford Robinson Gifford to Magoon, Elias L., 7 June 1859 (7.60)
- Boughton, George Henry to Magoon, Elias L., 4 July 1859 (7.61)
- Duncanson, R.S. to Magoon, Elias L., 16 Feb 1861 (7.62)